[00:00.36] 
[00:01.85] 
[00:03.92] 
[00:07.05] 
[00:09.60] 
[00:11.71] 
[00:15.39] 
[00:19.03] 
[00:25.93] 
[00:28.76] 
[00:34.61] 
[00:36.12] 
[00:37.72] 
[00:40.00] 
[00:42.93] 
[00:47.65] 
[00:48.45] 
[00:52.98] 
[00:55.81] 
[00:58.59] 
[01:00.25] 
[01:04.52] 
[01:05.64] 
[01:08.10] 
[01:13.72] 
[01:21.38] 
[01:23.40] 
[01:29.18] 
[01:32.50] 
[01:36.82] 
[01:40.95] 
[01:43.07] 
[01:48.17] 
[01:51.73] 
[01:54.07] 
[01:57.14] 
[01:58.81] 
[02:04.64] 
[02:08.10] 
[02:13.34] 
[02:18.50] 
[02:20.80] 
[02:23.69] 
[02:26.49] 
[02:30.55] 
[02:34.36] 
[02:36.16] 
[02:38.40] 
[02:41.77] 
[02:43.16] 
[02:45.82] 
[02:48.60] 
[02:50.03] 
[02:53.17] 
[02:56.95] 
[02:59.46] 
[03:03.96] 
[03:08.14] 
[03:10.00] 
[03:11.23] 
[03:14.25] 
[03:19.01] 
[03:22.52] 
[03:26.95] 
[03:29.82] 
[03:34.53] 
[03:36.34] 
[03:39.52] 
[03:41.90] 
[03:42.97] 
[03:44.62] 
[03:46.20] 
[03:50.36] 
[03:51.86] 
[03:53.79] 
[03:57.14] 
[03:59.74] 
[04:01.41] 
[04:03.92] 
[04:05.38] 
[04:08.72] 
[04:10.07] 
[04:12.70] 
[04:17.87] 
[04:20.40] 
[04:26.23] 
[04:30.88] 
[04:35.82] 
[04:38.28] 
[04:39.44] 
[04:40.56] 
[04:43.58] 
[04:45.58] 
[04:51.70] 
[04:52.46] 
[04:58.90] 
[05:02.99] 
[05:06.88] 
[05:08.05] 
[05:10.04] 
[05:15.18] 
[05:18.13] 
[05:18.99] 
[05:23.18] 
[05:26.49] 
[05:33.73] 
[05:35.50] 
[05:38.31] 
[05:39.20] 
[05:45.90] 
[05:51.26] 
[05:54.41] 
[05:57.64] 
[06:02.20] 
[06:04.52] 
[06:05.94] 
[06:08.17] 
[06:09.54] 
[06:14.79] 
[06:20.57] 
[06:22.63] 
[06:25.77] 
[06:31.85] 
[06:37.66] 
[06:42.67] 
[06:47.62] 
[06:49.57] 
[06:50.45] 
[06:55.51] 
[06:57.70] 
[06:58.86] 
[07:01.62] 
[07:06.01] 
[07:09.38] 
[07:11.32] 
[07:13.60] 
[07:14.82] 
[07:18.87] 
[07:22.22] 
[07:23.34] 
[07:26.33] 
[07:29.46] 
[07:32.08] 
[07:34.29] 
[07:37.96] 
[07:42.37] 
[07:44.42] 
[07:46.32] 
[07:48.43] 
[07:50.29] 
[07:56.30] 
[07:58.38] 
[08:03.64] 
[08:05.75] 
[08:07.44] 
[08:09.92] 
[08:13.28] 
[08:19.04] 
[08:22.19] 
[08:23.63] 
[08:25.35] 
[08:26.91] 
[08:29.47] 
[08:31.57] 
[08:33.76] 
[08:36.50] 
[08:37.80] 
[08:43.14] 
[08:45.41] 
[08:47.08] 
[08:48.11] 
[08:54.40] 
[08:56.70] 
[09:01.57] 
[09:04.82] 
[09:06.20] 
[09:09.04] 
[09:12.02] 
[09:15.16] 
[09:17.69] 
[09:21.52] 
[09:23.31] 
[09:24.11] 
[09:28.62] 
[09:31.99] 
[09:35.08] 
[09:39.84] 
[09:41.12] 
[09:42.62] 
[09:45.41] 
[09:47.22] 
[09:49.87] 
[09:54.70] 
[09:56.79] 
[09:58.88] 
[10:02.81] 
[10:08.38] 
[10:12.21] 
[10:15.28] 
[10:20.89] 
[10:23.82] 
[10:25.71] 
[10:30.26] 
