[00:00.00] 
[00:00.06] 
[00:03.26] 
[00:08.52] 
[00:12.86] 
[00:16.68] 
[00:21.58] 
[00:27.02] 
[00:35.15] 
[00:41.00] 
[00:43.81] 
[00:49.20] 
[00:52.54] 
[00:57.63] 
[01:05.47] 
[01:16.66] 
[01:21.71] 
[01:24.74] 
[01:28.96] 
[01:33.40] 
[01:36.15] 
[01:39.79] 
[01:45.11] 
[01:47.24] 
[01:54.37] 
[01:57.95] 
[02:03.20] 
[02:07.01] 
[02:09.30] 
[02:11.81] 
[02:16.46] 
[02:19.61] 
[02:23.56] 
[02:27.25] 
[02:31.66] 
[02:36.77] 
[02:41.46] 
[02:43.28] 
[02:45.44] 
[02:48.59] 
[02:51.96] 
[02:53.98] 
[03:00.55] 
[03:04.97] 
[03:08.26] 
[03:12.88] 
[03:18.69] 
[03:24.09] 
[03:29.51] 
[03:31.80] 
[03:33.55] 
[03:39.53] 
[03:45.55] 
[03:49.66] 
[03:53.66] 
[03:57.95] 
[03:59.72] 
[04:02.78] 
[04:06.24] 
[04:12.32] 
[04:17.34] 
[04:19.87] 
[04:23.77] 
[04:27.14] 
[04:28.95] 
[04:31.88] 
[04:33.22] 
[04:35.13] 
[04:39.43] 
[04:41.74] 
[04:44.62] 
[04:45.98] 
[04:49.15] 
[04:53.54] 
[04:55.61] 
[04:59.18] 
[05:02.36] 
[05:08.17] 
[05:11.05] 
[05:14.96] 
[05:16.97] 
[05:17.72] 
[05:24.96] 
[05:28.35] 
[05:32.02] 
[05:35.47] 
[05:40.88] 
[05:42.18] 
[05:45.11] 
[05:51.08] 
[05:54.31] 
[05:58.28] 
[05:59.78] 
[06:01.32] 
[06:01.91] 
[06:03.41] 
[06:06.41] 
[06:07.49] 
