we begin this hour with the latest tit
for tat between the US and China one day
after the United States accused two
Chinese citizens of carrying out an
extensive hacking campaign to steal data
from American companies China is now
firing back defending itself huge and
floatin a million the Chinese government
has never participated or supported
anyone in stealing business secrets for
a long time the relevant US departments
have been conducting organized and
large-scale cyber espionage and
surveillance on a lot of individuals and
organizations it has been an OD secret
and it doesn't end there
Rachel Blevins breaks it all down for us
the tit for tat battle between the
United States and China continues to
escalate and now China is accusing the
u.s. of fabricating facts in its cyber
hacking claims these latest accusations
come after the u.s. charged two Chinese
nationals with stealing trade secrets
from American government agencies
according to an unsealed indictment the
two alleged hackers were able to breach
computers of more than 45 entities in a
variety of industries including aviation
space and pharmaceutical technology all
on behalf of the Chinese military the
Department of Justice claims that the
suspects were part of a group called apt
10 that had dozens of computers in at
least a dozen countries the charges
include conspiracy to commit computer
intrusions against dozens of companies
in the United States and around the
world
the DOJ went on to accuse the group of
quote outright cheating and theft and
claim that it's alleged actions gave
China and unfair advantage at the
expense of law-abiding businesses and
countries but China is claiming that the
United States is the one that is
responsible for cyber espionage a
spokesperson for the country's Ministry
of Foreign Affairs demanded in a
Media tend to what she called fabricated
facts maybe well the u.s. is the biggest
power in the world but it is arrogant
and selfish and plays hard to suppress
the legitimate development rights of
other countries out of its own pursuit
of hegemony and Merrill mind it even
fabricated maxim this does not match his
status as a big powers this kind of us
is not good for peace and development
well it does not appear that the two
individuals named in the indictment have
been taken into custody the United
States claimed that more than a dozen
countries were affected by the alleged
hack could have a major impact now the
UK has joined with the US and has
publicly claimed that this campaign is
one of the most significant and
widespread cyber intrusions against the
UK and its allies that has been
uncovered to date with the intent to
target trade secrets and economic
interest around the world so while a
range of claims have been made by both
sides in this conflict it still remains
to be seen whether the countries
involved will actively retaliate and if
any evidence of the alleged cyber
hacking claims will be made public in
Washington Rachel Blevins RT and joining
me now to discuss investigative
journalist Ben Swan hey there Ben so
things appeared to be easing up though
between the US and China trade talks
were back underway and then BAM the u.s.
calls Canada to arrest the the Huawei
CFO and now this so what do you make of
the current us-china relations well I
think that as you said you know it
seemed like things were kind of on track
and things were going well
and then all of a sudden we ended up in
this situation that where it becomes
very messy obviously the arrests of the
CFO was a very big deal China's very
upset about it it's having big
ramifications for Canada as well but I
think the other thing that's taking
place here is that we know there's this
back and forth over tariffs right now on
and I wonder how much of that is playing
into this which side is going to get the
upper hand in terms of trade tariffs and
and how that plays out and how much of
what's going on right now is kind of a
falling over that backdrop and let's
let's talk about cybersecurity I know
that's really in your wheelhouse they're
experts all over the country say that
China has been on a global tear in the
way of cyber espionage ever since at
least 2014 and believe that it's China
that's really America's number one
threat in this new century do you agree
with that sentiment so cyber security is
a very big deal and is China the biggest
threat maybe I think there's a you could
make a very strong case for the idea
that China is here's the problem is that
everyone's hands are so dirty when it
comes to cyber security the u.s. is in
such a mess of its own obviously you go
back into 2014 in Edward Snowden and all
the stuff that came out about what the
NSA had been doing in the US government
have been doing spying on foreign
leaders hacking emails of Americans and
people internationally but there's a lot
of issues here but that doesn't mean
that China is it's okay for trying to do
whatever they're doing it's just that
everyone is such a dirty player in this
space and so many of these governments
are that it's hard to say well this is
the biggest threat this one's the most
dangerous because we're all doing it all
these nations are doing it to each other
if everyone would stop maybe we could
figure out what the bad players are but
no one wants to stop they just want to
say well we're not as bad as they are or
we have to do it because they're doing
it true but now another flash point in
us-china relations is is over the South
China Sea the Chinese continue to build
up their naval fleet there the US and
its allies find this to be some sort of
threat first why is this a threat to the
US and what do you view would be a fair
response to counter China's actions
there well look as someone who believes
the US needs to be involved in far fewer
interventions around the world you know
we know that the u.s. loves to flex its
military muscle we spend so much money
on military so everything you know we s
when you're a hammer everything looks
like a nail right and so that's how they
you as a military sees everything and
yet you know you look at what's
happening in the South China Sea how
does that really affect the US and u.s.
sovereignty and the security of the
United States it's not like China is
building up
fleets on the coast of Maine now doing
this in the Gulf of Mexico right and so
I think that's one of the the problems
with the with the narrative that every
time any government does anything
military wise the US has to respond in
some military way to continue to be what
policeman of the world to flex its
military might I just I don't think that
it's necessary for the u.s. to respond
every time another government in its own
corner of the world does something now
last Ben I want you to listen to what
the Chinese foreign ministry
spokesperson had to say and I want to
get your response on the other side we
urged the u.s. to immediately correct
its wrong actions stop slandering and
blackening China on the cybersecurity
issue and withdraw the so called
indictment of Chinese citizens so as to
avoid serious damage to china-us
relations in bilateral cooperation and
relevant fields is that fair is the US
making an example of these guys I think
the u.s. is trying to make an example of
them and you know when you consider that
that the arrest of the CFO right is that
would be the equivalency of someone like
a Tim Cook from Apple being arrested in
Beijing and the Chinese government
holding them if that were to happen the
US would for lack of a better term flip
its wig right nuts if that were to
happen to a prominent CEO or CFO of a
major US tech company and yet - for the
u.s. to be involved in this the US and
Canada - to have the CFO arrested and
want her in sent to the United States
and and AW extradite is the word I'm
looking for all these things that are
taking place yeah I think that it's
reasonable that China is upset about
this for for people who look at that and
say well I you know why is China so
upset just imagine if the shoe were on
the other foot and the analyst would see
it as an attack on US Authority u.s.
sovereignty you know as being the
biggest player in the world so I
understand why the Chinese are about it
again I think a lot of it just comes
back to everyone's hands so dirty on so
many of these levels all right we gotta
leave it right there thanks so much for
that as always been Swann hey YouTube
thanks for checking out our Channel we
hope you enjoyed the video we have tons
of content for you just like this for
more of Artie America's one-of-a-kind
news and analysis be sure to subscribe
and never stop questioning more